middleeasy.com 2017-02-10

# Privacy Policy - MiddleEasy.com

The following Privacy Policy governs the online information collection practices of MiddleEasy.com (“we” or “us”). Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you while you are using the MiddleEasy.com website (the “Site”), and the ways in which we use this information. This Privacy Policy, including our children’s privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means (for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail).

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of our Site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. Because the Web is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we will post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this website and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the Site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified.  
Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to:

Online Privacy Coordinator

7950 Jones Branch Drive

McLean, VA 22107

How We Collect and Use Information

We may collect and store personal or other information that you voluntarily supply to us online while using the Site (e.g., while on the Site or in responding via email to a feature provided on the Site).

We also collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate online through the Site. For example, we may collect information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, which allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic on the Site. We also may use a standard feature found in browser software called a “cookie” to enhance your experience with the Site. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us deliver advertisements, identify how many unique users visit us, and track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the Site where you may have entered preference information before. The Site also may use web beacons (single-pixel graphic files also known as “transparent GIFs”) to access cookies and to count users who visit the Site or open HTML-formatted email messages.

We use the information we collect from you while you are using the Site in a variety of ways, including using the information to customize features and advertising that appear on the Site. We also may provide your information to third parties, such as service providers, contractors, and advertisers, for a variety of purposes. Unless you inform us in accordance with the process described below, we reserve the right to use, and to disclose to third parties, all of the information collected from and about you while you are using the Site in any way and for any purpose, such as to enable us or a third party to provide you with information about products and services. If you do not wish your information to be used for these purposes, you must send a letter to the Online Privacy Coordinator whose address is listed at the end of this Privacy Policy requesting to be taken off any lists of information that may be used for these purposes or that may be given or sold to third-parties.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties online – for example on message boards, web logs, through email, or in chat areas – that information can be seen, collected and used by others besides us. We cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information.

Some of our third-party advertisers and ad servers that place and present advertising on the Site also may collect information from you via cookies, web beacons or similar technologies. These third-party advertisers and ad servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness, or for other purposes. The use and collection of your information by these third-party advertisers and ad servers is governed by the relevant third party’s privacy policy and is not covered by our Privacy Policy. Indeed, the privacy policies of these third-party advertisers and ad servers may be different from ours. If you have any concerns about a third party’s use of cookies or web beacons or use of your information, you should visit that party’s website and review its privacy policy.

The Site may also include links to other websites and provide access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third-party products or services through the Site, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

We also make some content, products and services available through our Site through cooperative relationships with third-party providers, where the brands of our provider partner appear on the Site in connection with such content, products and/or services. We may share with our provider partner any information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in cooperation with our provider partner. In some cases, the provider partner may collect information from you directly, in which cases the privacy policy of our provider partner may apply to the provider partner’s use of your information. The privacy policy of our provider partners may differ from ours. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners, you should contact the provider partner directly for more information.

Be aware that we may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Terms of Service agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of the Site or the public.

Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we sell some or all of our assets, or one or more of our websites is acquired by another company, information about our users may be among the transferred assets.  
Children’s Privacy Statement

This children’s privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, and provides important information regarding their rights under federal law with respect to such information.

We adhere to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and the guidelines of the Children’s Advertising Review Unit (CARU) of the Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc with respect to each of our websites directed at children. Parents should monitor their children’s online use and instruct their children never to provide personal information on the Site or on any other site without their parent’s permission.

If you are under 18, please be sure to read this Privacy Policy with your parents or legal guardians and ask questions about things you do not understand. Children under 13 must get their parent’s or legal guardian’s permission before giving out their email address or any personal information to us or to anyone else on the Internet.

We do not collect personal information online from children under 13 without consent of a parent or legal guardian except in special, limited circumstances as permitted by law. If a child is under 13 and wants to use the Site to access special features, like scavenger hunts, personalized pages, games or clubs, we might ask that child to “register.” They can often do so anonymously by just providing a user name and password, but sometimes we need a child’s first name and email address. When we ask for a child’s first name, that child is encouraged to use a “screen name” (not their real name) that only they know. Sometimes we will ask a child to make up a special password so that only they can see their customized areas on the Site. We may collect personal information from a child such as a last name, address or email address when the information is necessary for a particular activity, and only with the verifiable consent of that child’s parent. If we need more than just a child’s first name (or screen name) and email address for that child to participate in a particular online activity, we will ask that child for their parent’s email or mailing address so that we can notify the parent of their child’s request and get the parent’s permission. When we ask for the parent’s permission, we will tell the parent what we will do with the information the parent or the child provides us, and we will tell the parent how they can review their child’s information and ask us to delete the information. We do not keep a child’s email address unless the parent tells us it is okay.

We might collect an email address and first name (or screen name) from a child under 13 without their parent’s consent, but only in the following special cases:

If a child under 13 sends a request to us, we keep the child’s email address for long enough to respond to them. We delete this information from our system after we answer the child’s question.  
If a child under 13 signs up for an email newsletter, or other activity that requires multiple online contact with the child, we also ask the child for a parent’s or legal guardian’s email address so we can notify the child’s parent and give the parent an opportunity to opt out.  
Occasionally, we have special site activities or promotions like sweepstakes or contests that are open to children even if they are under 13. If a child under 13 signs up for such an activity or promotion, we also ask the child for a parent’s or legal guardian’s email address so we can notify the child’s parent and give the parent an opportunity to opt out.

If we need more than an email address and first name (or screen name) to enter a child under 13 in a promotion or allow the child to participate in an activity on the Site, we will notify that child’s parents, explain what information we need and why, and generally ask that parent (not the child) to provide it. For instance, we might ask a parent for their mailing address so that we can send to that parent, for their child, any prizes their child wins, or for a parent’s telephone number so that we can tell that parent when their child has won. Any information a parent or a child gives us in the above special circumstances will be deleted from our database once the promotion, program or activity is concluded, and after any legally required period for keeping such information is complete.

We do not require a child under 13 to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in a contest, game or other activity as a condition of participation. If a parent no longer wishes their child who is under 13 to participate in an email newsletter, that parent can simply click on the link that is provided for removal or contact us at.

Upon proper identification, parents or legal guardians may review the personal information we have collected about their child who is under 13, request deletion, or refuse to allow further collection or use of the information. Click here to print a copy of our Personal Information Review Access Request, fill it out completely and mail it to:

Online Privacy Coordinator

7950 Jones Branch Drive

McLean, VA 22107

However, if a parent asks us to delete the information for their child who is under 13, we may have to ask that child not to participate in our activities.  
How To Make Changes to Your Information

If you have provided information about yourself on the Site, you may change, modify, and/or delete your information at any time by visiting MiddleEasy.com.  
Questions Regarding Privacy

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our privacy practices, or your dealings with us, you can contact:

Online Privacy Coordinator

7950 Jones Branch Drive

McLean, VA 22107
